wiki-errors.com 2019-08-04

# Privacy policy « wiki-errors.com

BY ACCESSING THIS SITE YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT.

WIKI-ERRORS.COM is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy will detail how we will treat any and all information that you provide us with. This covers all the web properties that are owned and operated by WIKI-ERRORS.COM.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

Contact Information such as name and email address.

## We use this information to

Respond to customer service requests  
Respond to your questions and concerns  
Allow you to post blog comments

We will not share your personal information with third parties, and we will not send any marketing emails.

## Opt-Out and Un-Subscription

Currently we do not send marketing emails.

We, WIKI-ERRORS.COM only send email to you on transactional or service related,such as a confirmation email after the review posting.You can opt-out of these service related emails by emailing us at optout@wiki-errors.com or contact us through [Contact us](http://wiki-errors.com/contact-us/)

## What We Do With Your Personal Data

All the personal information you provide us with is used to enhance your user experience. We use personal information to help us with demographics and your information allows us to personally greet you when you revisit our site. We also use the information to know what type of advertising would best be suited for your personal needs. You can request for us to send or not send you advertising at the time of your registration.

## Information Collected

WIKI-ERRORS.COM may collect information from the user at various points, but that information will be kept only by WIKI-ERRORS.COM and not viewed by others.

## Sharing Information Collected

WIKI-ERRORS.COM does not collect any personal information and unless it is provide by you, WIKI-ERRORS.COM will not collect it. WIKI-ERRORS.COM does not rent, sell, or share any information that you provide with any other group or organization. WIKI-ERRORS.COM strives to always protect your information and will only share it if required to do so by law and will then only share it with law enforcement agencies or government agencies. ****

## Information Use

With the exception of use required by law, WIKI-ERRORS.COM does not disclose any information, including e-mail addresses, with any other third party organization.

## Log Files

WIKI-ERRORS.COM’s website will use log files in order to analyze trends and track user movement, but no personal information will be used with these logs. Instead, WIKI-ERRORS.COM uses IP addresses, which are not linked to any personal information.

## Cookies

WIKI-ERRORS.COM uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. These cookies are a small piece of data that are stored on your computer tied to information about you. The session cookies will expire on their own and you can get rid of persistent cookies at any time by following your browser help files.

Some advertisers will use these cookies on the WIKI-ERRORS.COM site, however WIKI-ERRORS.COM has no control over such actions. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by WIKI-ERRORS.COM only.

## Spam

WIKI-ERRORS.COM has a zero tolerance for any abuse of this privacy policy or spam.

## Third Party Intermediaries

WIKI-ERRORS.COM uses an outside credit card processing company to bill for various goods and/or services. This company does not store, sell, or retain any of your personal information for secondary purposes.

## Links to Other Sites

WIKI-ERRORS.COM has various links to websites that are not under our control WIKI-ERRORS.COM warns all users to be aware when leaving our website for another as WIKI-ERRORS.COM cannot control the action of these other websites. Any collected information from said websites is not covered under this privacy policy.

## Surveys

WIKI-ERRORS.COM conducts surveys from time to time using an intermediary company. These surveys are strictly voluntary and any information gathered in these surveys is kept strictly confidential. Personal information collected in a survey will not be sold, rented, or distributed to any other third party.

## Update Personal Information

WIKI-ERRORS.COM provides users with a way to update or change personal information at any time.

## Changes in Privacy Policy

WIKI-ERRORS.COM will always post any changes to the privacy policy on this page and at other appropriate places. If any changes take place in regards to the way WIKI-ERRORS.COM collects and/or distributes information, it will first be disclosed.

## Contact Information

If you contact WIKI-ERRORS.COM through any link with personal information, that information will not be used to contact you. WIKI-ERRORS.COM will not sell or share this information with any third party.

## Information Collected By Payment Processing System:

1- Clickbank is our credit card processing system. Please view Clickbank’s [privacy policy ](https://accounts.clickbank.com/privacy.html)for more information.

2- Safecart is our credit card processing system. Please view Safecart’s privacy policy for more information: Safecart customer privacy policy

https://support.safecart.com/privacy
